[{"answer": "So uh ... Maybe we could uh ..", "docId": "pleasantville.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": " Cool", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "What department store did they go to", "docId": "pleasantville.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "my friend's", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": " God, my friend. Just give it to me", "docId": "pleasantville.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "YOU get lost", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "Yo", "docId": "pleasantville.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "Because we don't belong", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": " I still don't see why we're doing this", "docId": "pleasantville.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "We're supposed to be at home my friend! We're supposed to be in color!  Oh God ..", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Okay, now you listen to me! I don't know what's going on but you'd better fix it! I had a date with my friend and I even bought new UNDERWEAR", "docId": "pleasantville.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Play along", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "my friend. Captain of the basketball team", "docId": "pleasantville.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "As a matter of fact he does", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "He won't notice anyway", "docId": "pleasantville.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "They don't notice that kind of thing", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": " But where would we go", "docId": "pleasantville.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": " Lover's Lane", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": " I baked you my oatmeal cookies", "docId": "pleasantville.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "No. I baked them for you", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": " Oh, no ... You baked those for my friend", "docId": "pleasantville.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "No. You baked them for my friend", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "No. I baked them for you", "docId": "pleasantville.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": " No. I baked them for you", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Looks just like it did", "docId": "pleasantville.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": " No ... They won't be able to tell", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "What's wrong", "docId": "pleasantville.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "Nothing", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "No. She really liked you", "docId": "pleasantville.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "Gone out with you. She woulda like rearranged your tonsils", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "Do they have those ... Where you come from", "docId": "pleasantville.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "You don't know", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": " Look at me my friend. That meeting's not for me. Look at my face", "docId": "pleasantville.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "I don't want to put on some make up ..", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": " I made a couple of lunches for you and put them in brown paper bags ...  I'm gonna go now", "docId": "pleasantville.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "I'm gonna go now", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": "my friend's got a blue front door", "docId": "pleasantville.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Not that blue", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "my friend! Arrest them", "docId": "pleasantville.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "What do you mean!", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "Green", "docId": "pleasantville.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "The other one", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": " It's not in ME", "docId": "pleasantville.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "No it isn't", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "I'm so proud of you, my friend", "docId": "pleasantville.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "I love you too", "qsentId": 46}]